I did not wanna do this...
...but I have here the rare,
mint-condition, production-era...
...Star Trek: The Next Generation
Geordi La Forge without his VISOR...
...in the original packaging.
If you do not get out of my way...
...I will open it.
(Howard:)Okay, man, be cool.
(Howard:)We're all friends here.
(Penny(coming out of her flat):)What the hell's going on?
- You hypocrite.
- What?
Little Miss Grown-Ups-
Don't-Play-With-Toys.
If I went into that apartment right now,
would I not find Beanie Babies?
(Sheldon:)Are you not an accumulator
of Care Bears and My Little Ponies?
(Sheldon:)And who is that Japanese feline
I see frolicking on your shorts?
Hello, Hello Kitty.
(Penny:)Okay, okay, look,
if this is about yesterday, Leonard...
(Penny:)...I am really sorry about what I said.
I was just upset.
- No, I needed to hear it.
- You didn't. You are a great guy.
And it is the things you love
that make you who you are.
(Howard:)I guess that makes me large breasts.